Ace, Luffy, Listen!
The three of us, we're
gonna leave this country!
We're gonna sail the seas
and see the whole world!
From now on, we're
honest-to-goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
Brothers!
How long are you going to
lay there like a moron?
By the way, the treasure we were
keeping in the forest is gone.
Someone must have gotten to it.
Meh, I don't care about the treasure.
Not anymore.
I mean, those were pirate
savings I was sharing with Sabo.
And you, too, later on, I guess.
But in the end, he didn't
need money to set sail.
So why should I get bent
out of shape about it?
After all, what's the point in having
treasure if you can't even protect it?
Hey, Ace!
I...
I wanna get stronger!
be the strongest in the world and then
I'll protect everyone I will lose Anyone
I care about you gotta make me a promise
I'm begging you please
don't Don't die, Gaze!
Cut it out.
You ought to be worried
about dying before I do.
What, did you forget you're
a lot weaker than me?
Listen, and you listen up good.
I'm never going to die.
You know, Sabo told me
to take care of you.
So I promise, I'm not
gonna die, okay? Not ever.
At least not as long as I've got a wussy
little brother who needs me to protect him.
Yeah, okay.
Smarts aren't exactly my strong point,
so I still don't really
understand why Sabo was killed.
But whoever did it,
they must be opposed
to freedom because they
shot him down before he
ever got a taste of it.
But we shared that same cup of sake
with him, and we're still alive.
Luffy, listen to me, okay?
There's just one way to live
and that's without any regrets.
Boys from families like
mine once they turn
18 they're officially
registered as nobles.
That's why I'm leaving.
I gotta be gone before I'm 17.
Someday.
We're gonna set sail just like Sabo.
We're gonna live the way we wanna live.
More free than anyone else.
But you know what that means?
We'll make plenty of
enemies along the way.
We're gonna have to
fight Garp someday I bet.
We gotta be willing to risk everything.
Let's go out to sea at 17,
just like Sabo planned.
Then, we'll be pirates.
I love you.
Oh I know what I'm supposed to do?
Don't let go down, don't be able to shine!
The battle of the world
is the end of the world!
I am not going to hurt you, but
I don't want to do anything?
If you open the door, you
will be able to open the door.
Let's start with the new world.
We fight together.
I believe.
I will connect to the future.
I will never be able to see you.
I will never be able to forget.
Don't forget, we fight together.
The world noble's visit to the
Goa Kingdom has come and gone.
But another visitor lingers at a
small village in the East Blue.
A group of aspiring swordsmen
chat about the strange encounter.
Did you see that weird guy
with the big head? Yes.
Face was totally crazy too.
I I bet he needs that giant
ship to fit his giant head.
580, 581,
582, 583, 584.
You certainly kept me waiting.
What could possibly be
more important than me?
Sorry.
Oh, goodness.
Is that...
Someone get help.
This doesn't look good.
Let's prepare treatment.
Roger.
Honestly, what in the world
have you been up to all day?
I was watching the ceremony
they held for the World Noble.
Ah!
One, that's some risky business,
and two, why didn't you take me?
Because you would attract too
much attention, obviously.
Could it be I'm too fabulous?
At any rate, we've
tarried for long enough.
We've got business to attend to.
Do we have supplies?
The training hall at the village
gave us just enough food for now.
Very well.
Set sail.
We're heading back to Baltico.
A short time later, in
the nearby Goa Kingdom.
Ah!
Finally, some junk!
Although the fire raised Grey
Terminal and its people to the ground,
another sea of trash and another
sea of scavengers appeared.
You're in for it this time!
Here it goes!
Now go! Go!
Pistol!
Are you kidding me?
You still suck butt.
It doesn't matter how hard you
punch if you can't hit anything.
I told you, rubber's a crappy power.
It's no good for fighting.
Shut up! You're dumb!
You're the dumb one!
I'm honest, that's all!
I'm trying to save you from falling
on your stupid rubber ass all day!
You're just jealous because you
can't do all some stuff like me!
All you've got are jerk powers and I'm
working on all kinds of cool moves!
Luffy, that was great!
Man, that punch of yours flies further
and further every day! Come on!
If you go easy on him,
he'll get a big head!
I got stronger today and I'm
gonna be even stronger tomorrow!
Right, Sabo?
This Abba was a nice
brother, not like you.
You're trying to say it'd be
better if I died, aren't you?
Ow. Huh?
I'm hereby establishing my own country.
He's doing what now?
What are you little idiots up to now?
We need to be strong
enough to live on our own!
You're from the Dadan kingdom, by the way.
We still need to use your bath though.
Ahhhh...
Ace, this one is way too
big, I need your help! You?
The mighty King Luffy needs help?
Here goes!
No!
Hey, it's the Dawn Kingdom! We need help!
Luffy got hurt!
He's in trouble!
Magra!
Hurry up! This is bad!
Okay, Ace.
Hurry, bring him inside.
Okay, wow.
It's a good thing you brought
him here when you did.
Also, if this cut had been any deeper,
he probably would have died on the spot.
I hate to say it, but this is
no good with only two of you.
It's all my fault.
I knew better.
Even if you're a captain, fighting
alone doesn't make you any stronger.
I'm still no good.
I'm still not good enough.
No, no.
I'm sorry, Luffy.
I let you down.
Guys, come see!
Makino came to visit,
and she brought booze!
You want to know how to
properly say thank you?
Mm-hmm.
And what's this about paying respects?
As a pirate and as Luffy's big brother,
I need to pay my respects
to this Shanks guy.
Luffy says he owes the man his life,
so it's kind of the least I can do.
Got something to say to me?
Sorry, sorry.
Okay, I think I can give you some tips.
For starters, after a meal...
It's a dining dish!
Come back!
Wait a sec, we almost forgot.
Gotta pay respect. Oops!
Yeah, you're right!
Oh?
Thank you for the meal, sir.
Ah! Keep your thanks!
Are you brats gonna pay me or what?
I'm not losing today! No way!
All right, now it's time to go!
Now for some bare meat stew!
Take care, Ace. See ya!
Yeah!
See you soon!
Keep training hard!
Just give me three years
and before you know it,
my wanted poster's gonna
be everywhere you go!
Kick some ass!
Bon voyage!
Don't catch a cold out there!
Look for me in the papers.
It won't take long, okay?
The world did not know that the son
of Gol Roger had grown up in secret,
nor did they know that he set sail that
day, determined to make a name of his own.
Yes, that's it, huh?
Honestly, if Garp were here,
think of what he'd say.
Gonna need you to raise
this baby for me. What? Why?
Is it even yours?
So there you are, boss.
Hey, believe it or not, Ace is gone.
That's so well.
One last brat to worry about, though.
I'm sure Garp will give me hell for it.
Kid left, and he's still
causing me trouble.
Oh, I almost forgot.
There's a message he
asked us to give to you.
Yeah, why should I care?
He probably just wants to tell
me my feet smell or something.
He said, thank you for taking care of me.
How could you do that to me, you beast?
What's wrong, boss?
You're not crying, are you?
If you don't shut up, I'll make you cry!
Three more years, that's the rule!
Now gum-gum-pistol!
So close!
I just need a little more!
You almost got it now, Luffy.
Bend your legs a little
and aim straight ahead.
Now gum-gum-pistol!
Gotta keep getting stronger!
Hang on, Ace!
I'm coming for you!
Luffy!
Hey, you gotta see the paper, look.
Oh, what's up?
It's just like he said.
Whoa, you're right, Ace made the news.
He's got a ship and a crew and everything.
Oh man, I'm so jealous, wow.
But I'm gonna do even better.
Hey, you guys!
I'm leaving now, you're
not gonna see me off? Hey!
Use your head for once.
The mayor and Makino
wouldn't mind us stopping by,
but as for everyone else
in Windmill Village,
we'd probably scare the
pants right off them.
I don't know...
Ugh, don't make it
awkward, just go already!
Okay.
Well, goodbye, you guys!
Thanks for everything!
I'm sure gonna miss you!
Oh, now don't say that!
You're gonna make us blush!
Well, bye! Take it easy!
I will!
You guys too, okay?
Oh, one last thing!
Dad, I still think mountain
bandits are super lame!
Shut up and leave, dammit!
But you guys, you're great!
It's not enough to ruin my life.
Now you got to break my heart, too.
You're awful, I tell you.
All of you are good for nothing.
Sorry I made you cry.
Shut up or I'll make you cry.
Now to Windmill Village on Dawn
Island at the edge of the Goa Kingdom.
No offense, but why don't you take
my old fishing boat instead, Luffy?
That thing is going to sink
as soon as you get out to sea.
That's too small, even for you.
I want to start small, but
I'll get a real big one soon.
Don't worry.
Sabo!
Here I go!
Watch out for me out there, okay?
Sabo was first, and Ace was second.
I may be the last to go, but
I'm going to be the best.
I'm coming for you, Ace.
And all my special moves work now, too!
Why are you talking to yourself?
Is this some kind of
pirate ritual I don't get?
No, it's a challenge to my brother,
Ace. Ace? Who is that? I don't know.
Okay, I'm going for real now.
I knew this day would come,
but I'm still a bit sad.
I'll sure miss him.
Satisfied, like the world
needs another pirate.
Oh, perfect weather today. Lock me!
Hey!
Oh, no!
Hey, pal.
It's been a while, huh?
This won't play out like last time.
I've been practicing this
move for ten whole years!
Now, Gon-Gon!
Pistol!
Been waiting a long time to do that. Yeah!
Yay!
We just took out that
sea monster in one punch.
I gotta admit, I'm proud.
First, I need a crew.
About ten people should be enough.
After that, pirate flag.
All right!
Let's get going!
Someday I'm gonna be...
King of the Pirates!
But time has not been kind.
And after the death of Ace, Luffy's
optimism from that day is nowhere in sight.
Blaze, Luffy.
The King of the Pirates!
I'm so...
I'm so weak!
It's Garp!
Garp is back and he brought
his battleship! Should we run?
I read about the battle at
Marineford in the paper.
Congratulations on your victory!
Word travels fast these days, huh?
Is Luffy okay?
Now that Whitebeard's dead, the
pirates are going out of control.
Is that why you're here?
Things have gotten bad.
We're afraid to go out.
They're like vultures staring us down.
I don't mean to complain, but I'm
afraid they can invade any second now.
Not likely.
I just sunk three of them with
cannonballs on the way out here.
Really? Whoa.
They were nothing but
a bunch of blowhards.
All bark and no bite.
The seas are going to
be tense the world over
without Whitebeard to
scare off all the thugs.
Even if that's not the
Navy's official stance.
Anyway, since you're so far from our base,
I prepared a little something. See? Sir!
Security by Navy Vice Admiral Garp?
That'll scare them off for sure.
One look at that and
they'll straighten right up.
While you're here,
there's one more problem.
A bunch of mountain bandits
came down to the village.
They took over Maki-no's
bar and they aren't leaving.
That's all.
Please, calm down!
Hello, Garp.
Hey, that's one right there.
How dare you show your face here?
After what you've done!
Garp That's not good.
Var General
Back off, man!
She's a friend.
The hell I am!
You were right with them
on that battlefield?
Those poor boys and you didn't
do a damn thing to help them!
Why did you have me raise ace, huh?
Why did you have me take care of
them if it was good in this way?
You stood there and watched that boy die!
You care more about your
damn job than your family!
The great hero of the Navy!
I hope you're proud of yourself,
you heartless piece of crap!
Now, now, boss!
Take it easy!
Say something, you bastard!
Why didn't you help him?
Why didn't you do something?
Look me right in the face,
you spineless wretch!
You answer me, dammit!
Dejan, enough!
Knock it out.
How do you think he feels?
He's their grandfather.
He's suffering too.
He was right there and
he couldn't do a thing
You're wrong.
Garp is suffering.
No.
The only one who's really
suffering here is Luffy damn it.
Okay, so let's pretend Shanks
is here with you right now.
What do you say?
Hi, I'm Ace.
Who the hell are you? Boo!
I know you're pirates, but I
don't think he'd be impressed.
Yeah!
Be way more cool!
Fancy meeting you here. Boo!
Mister, what's your deal? Boo.
Because he didn't say punk?
Nope, nope.
Luffy, stop.
You're distracting poor Ace.
Go be stupid somewhere else.
We're learning here.
You little pest.
I'm not distracting.
Oh, yeah.
I found an anaconda nest filled with a
bunch of eggs and they're super huge.
Let's grab them and cook them up.
What?
Man, that sounds awesome.
No, not right now.
I'm gonna learn some
manners even if it kills me.
I can't go on my own.
What if the anaconda mom finds me?
But if you're there with
me, we can beat it for sure.
Come on, let's go.
I said no.
Luffy loved Ace more than
anything in the world.
Ragino.
Hey, Garp.
What happened to Luffy?
The newspaper said he went
missing after the war.
That he did.
The submarine carried him away.
The admirals attacked and tried
to stop him from escaping,
and afterwards they held a search.
But they couldn't find
a single trace of him.
There was no shipwreck,
so he's probably alive.
That's a relief.
Wait, so what's up with this bandit?
She obviously seems to know Garp, but
why did he let her punch him like that?
Yeah.
Luffy's been a little moron
since the day I met him.
But no matter what he does,
I'm always on his side.
As much as I'm hurting,
I know he's got it worse.
And it breaks my heart.
I know things are hard right
now, but don't you dare give up!
Meanwhile, far away and far along the Grand
Line, in a place known as the New World,
I don't know how I can
ever thank you enough.
No need to make a big deal out of it.
Whitebeard was a rival, but I still
held a lot of respect for the man.
Even Sengoku felt that way.
Well, I suppose it's time for us to go.
Yeah, thank you again.
I can only imagine how
tough this is on Luffy.
Even so, his brother died like a true man.
Take it back, or else.
You don't know anything about
the man who saved my life!
This is his era!
Don't you forget it!
Maybe Ace wouldn't want to hear this,
but that's exactly what
Captain Roger would have done.
There were times when I wished
he wasn't too bold to run away.
Too bold to shed tears.
Listen, Luffy, it's not only victory
that makes a man, but defeat,
joy and sorrow alike.
There's no shame in backing down.
There's no shame in crying.
So long as you overcome it.
Dammit!
I couldn't save my crew or my brother!
Luffy...
Go away!
Leave me alone!
I cannot.
Although I understand your pain, I will
not allow you to hurt yourself any more.
It's not your business!
This is my body!
What of Ace, then?
Who sacrificed his body to protect you?
Was that none of your business?
You bastard! Shut up!
Say one more word and I'm gonna crush you!
If that would make you happy,
then why don't you try?
But let me warn you injured though.
I am you will not defeat
me not in that condition
Let me tell you something.
A while back, when I
was hunting down Teach,
I went to Alabasta Kingdom, and I saw my
brother for the first time in three years.
As soon as I saw his face, a
weight lifted from my heart.
And do you know why?
Ow!
Are you insane?
Stop moving!
I've had enough of your nonsense!
Boy, you can't see a thing. You're blind.
You never doubted your strength.
But now,
the confidence that once allowed you to
soar above the clouds has been shattered.
Your brother who was your
guiding light has faded away.
and your enemy stands so
tall and casts so great a
shadow that you can do naught
but cower in the darkness.
And now, you strike out like an animal at
the cage your doubt has placed around you.
So long as you are consumed
by regret and guilt,
you will never find your way forward.
Luffy, your pain may be great,
but it mustn't devour you.
There is yet joy beyond your sorrows.
What's gone may be gone,
but you still have something left in
this world to treasure, don't you?
Hey, if you want to screw
around, go do it somewhere else.
I'm trying to build muscle here.
Luffy!
We've got a big storm on the horizon!
Make preparations, quick!
I had a big one.
You just missed it.
But the next one is
going to be even bigger.
Scram.
I'm almost done.
Just keep your pants on.
It's okay.
No matter how bad you're
hurt, you're in good hands.
By the way, this one
might sting a little bit.
Oh, Luffy.
If you like treasure, this
research is fascinating. Come see.
What's up, buddy?
If you're checking on the coal
engine, it's in super shape.
And if you're checking on
me, well, I'm super too.
Good morning, Captain Rise and Shine.
How about I play you a little song?
to really get those bones moving.
Luffy.
Captain Luffy!
Luffy!
My crew.
I still have my crew.
Zoro, Nami, Usopp, Sanji, Jumper,
Robin, Franky, and Brooke.
They're still out there waiting for me.
Now do you see?
I have to get back to this ship,
no matter how long it takes me.
Guys, meet back on the
sunny in three days! Roger!
Everything's a mess, and I'm already late.
But I have to make it back to Sabahodi.
I know they'll be there.
It wasn't just knowing he was
safe, or seeing him smile again.
When you've got a bungling kid brother
like me, you can't help but worry a bit.
He might be a bit much for all of you to
handle, but take good care of him for me.
I mean, sure, he wasn't the snot-nosed
kid following me around anymore,
but more than that, he had friends.
A crew that he could depend on.
No matter what, he'll be just fine.
So I don't have to worry anymore.
I wish they were here right now!
I miss them!
I miss my crew!